<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Detectivemail</title>
	<atom:link href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail</link>
	<description>Crime Stories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 20:11:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/wp-content/uploads/detectivemail-logo.jpg</url>
	<title>Detectivemail</title>
	<link>https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mr. Ghost &#124; Chapter 1</title>
		<link>https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/mr-ghost-chapter-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Md Mazidul Haque Farabi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Mr. Ghost]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mysteries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[author]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[case 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mr-ghost]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mr-ghost-chapter-1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mysteries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top rated]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/?p=1006</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>So the evil lady killer was brought under justice. The state&#8217;s security division was somewhat impressed by the two foreign detectives&#8217; works and wanted to keep them anyway. And accordingly, a one-year contract for the detectives was sent to both their respective countries with a view of additional investigation and related help in the upcoming &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/mr-ghost-chapter-1/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Mr. Ghost &#124; Chapter 1</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/mr-ghost-chapter-1/">Mr. Ghost | Chapter 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="1006" class="elementor elementor-1006" data-elementor-settings="[]">
							<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-3598bbe elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="3598bbe" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-d5c210d" data-id="d5c210d" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-691e3aa elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="691e3aa" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
															<img width="768" height="510" src="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/wp-content/uploads/mr-ghost-chapter-one.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large" alt="" />															</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-08a4499 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="08a4499" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-57679ad" data-id="57679ad" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-bd9ccbe elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="bd9ccbe" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
								<p>So the evil lady killer was brought under justice. The state&#8217;s security division was somewhat impressed by the two foreign detectives&#8217; works and wanted to keep them anyway. And accordingly, a one-year contract for the detectives was sent to both their respective countries with a view of additional investigation and related help in the upcoming months. Though Alex and Miles would never willingly agree to stay, the paycheck was interesting enough to convince them. And even before they could realize how big an opportunity this was for them to enhance their career experience to another level, a bank robbery in the adjacent city made them re-think if the amount of money they were being paid was actually great.</p><p>McGill: 100 million dollars.<br />Miles: What?<br />McGill: Yes. Stolen. No alarm, no breaking-ins, no security breach, nothing! The money, it&#8217;s gone.<br />Alex: It&#8217;s been hacked and sent somewhere else by wire transfer.<br />McGill: Yes. But hacking doesn&#8217;t falsify that it was stolen. It was. And now, somehow, we&#8217;re responsible.<br />Miles: What? That&#8217;s absolutely insane. We have nothing to do. It didn&#8217;t even happen in our city.<br />McGill: Yeah, right. Try explaining that to people who lost their money. I think this is it. I&#8217;m unofficially suspended. They&#8217;re going to suspend three officers.<br />Alex: Oh, you guys are so wrong. We can do something. Come on, I know a guy.</p><p>Detective Alex took them to a house at a corner of Dublin. A guy opened the door as they knocked.</p><p>Guy: How may I help you – oh hey! Alex! How&#8217;s it going?<br />Alex: Fine, Johann. I need your help.<br />Johann: Oh yeah, absolutely – come in.</p><p>They went to Johann&#8217;s room, and it was a mess. He had this server, a highly powerful computer with triple adjusted monitors and all for – coding and gaming. He had this long blonde hair, a tall face, and by the looks, you can guess – a typical nerd. The round glasses again verify the statement.</p><p>Johann: So uh, your mates seem tense. What&#8217;s the problem?<br />Alex: 100 million dollars have been stolen. From Drogheda.<br />Johann: Yeah – I know, I know. So, it&#8217;s been hacked, I read.<br />Alex: Yes. Hacked. Now, we are assigned to find out who it is and where the money is. It&#8217;s a lot of money, Johann. The money of the people. We have to find him.<br />Miles: Are you going to help us?<br />Johann: Yes, of course, of course. Now. If you wanna know who it was, you have to first figure out how he did it.<br />Alex: Tell us.<br />Johann: (deep breath) you see, wire transfers are made with servers like TransFast. They are highly secure and maintain a very efficient level of encryption protocol. The greatest of the hackers have tried, but it&#8217;s something that cannot be hacked.<br />Alex: So how&#8217;s it even possible? You&#8217;re saying no one can hack that?<br />Johann: Yes, yes, exactly. Unless –<br />Alex: Unless what?<br />Johann: You have help from the inside.<br />Alex: Oh. I see.<br />McGill: So someone in the bank helped the hacker.<br />Johann: Yeah, but it&#8217;s not just someone. Someone with access to the Bank&#8217;s TransFast account. Now obviously, the suspicion goes to that officer. But you don&#8217;t have proof. Because the statistics would never recall him making that transfer.<br />McGill: So, that proves he didn&#8217;t do it?<br />Johann: No, you cannot say that he didn&#8217;t do it. He might&#8217;ve done it, might not. But the security was breached. And in these cases, obviously from a computer with a hidden IP address. Now, it isn&#8217;t that easy. (Smiles) otherwise, for a hundred million dollars, I would&#8217;ve done it myself.<br />McGill: (Clears throat).<br />Johann: Anyway, so, you guys know about the password hashing algorithm?<br />Miles: No idea.<br />Johann: It&#8217;s like, umm, whenever you create a password into an account, the password itself isn&#8217;t saved how it was precisely typed.<br />Alex: So?<br />Johann: So, um, what the algorithm does is that it takes in the input and converts the characters into a string of unknown numbers and variables. That&#8217;s what hashes like – MD5 and SHA-1 have been doing to this date.<br />Miles: Okay….<br />Johann: So um, it does that because if, and only if the site has a data breach, which can be easy to do for professional hackers; it doesn&#8217;t reveal the actual password. The password remains hidden. So whenever I say he had help from the inside, I mean he actually somehow got that data breach.<br />Alex: Okay, so he couldn&#8217;t do the whole work even with someone&#8217;s help?<br />Johann: Exactly! He still has to figure out the hash. And as for hashes, it&#8217;s a non-reversible function.<br />Alex: So? How he did it?<br />Johann: So, he has to be legit. What I mean is that either yes, he can use a probable wordlist with random passwords, but (laugh) you know, he&#8217;s not Sherlock Holmes. And the recent algorithms make it compulsory to add numbers and symbols to your password.<br />Miles: You&#8217;re saying he couldn&#8217;t have guessed the password?<br />Johann: Yeah, that&#8217;s about what I meant. So, he&#8217;s a hacker. He might do other than that, search for most commonly used words for passwords, and then get those respective hashes to match his breached data. If he&#8217;s lucky and anyone matches, he&#8217;s in! Then he can do things- like, transfer the money. 100 Mill is just a number. He just needed to press a single button, and that&#8217;s all then.<br />McGill: (Laughs) sounds about easy to me, but is that all?</p><p>Johann: Well, no. Because, um, yeah, first of all, he needs to be lucky enough to have the matching hash in his commonly used hashes database. I mean, a password can be literally anything, from your dog&#8217;s name to your favourite pornstar. There&#8217;s no database large enough to hold so many hashes, and even if it does, he&#8217;s gonna have a minimal number of attempts until the page crashes and the security breach attempt is notified to the people responsible for it. But they didn&#8217;t report anything like that, did they?<br />McGill: Nope.<br />Miles: What if they are included?<br />McGill: Why would they be included? It&#8217;s their bank, damn it!<br />Miles: Still, 100 Mill is a large number, don&#8217;t you think?<br />Johann: Come on, guys, if it was them, they wouldn&#8217;t even need to hack it in the first place. They&#8217;d just override and hit send, and that&#8217;s all.<br />Alex: We&#8217;ll investigate them. But I&#8217;d like you to continue. There&#8217;s no other way around?<br />Johann: Nothing that I can recall. But wait. I wasn&#8217;t finished.<br />Alex: What do you mean?<br />Johann: Salting algorithm. Now, modern sites use their sorting algorithm to mess with the hash, just for their last support.<br />Miles: What is that?<br />Johann: It&#8217;s like a hidden phrase of some random characters. Say, if their TransFast uses the salting algorithm of like, &#8217;22A9@&#8217;, this particular phrase will be hiddenly added to any area of the hashed password. Like, it can even be in the middle. And the hash is saved likewise. So, in that case, what happens is that, even if you found the hash with a breach, you can&#8217;t figure out the actual hash, neither the actual word. Because you don&#8217;t know their salting phrase and where it is used.<br />Alex: So much information. It just makes sense. No. It doesn&#8217;t add up. He must&#8217;ve had help from the inside.<br />Johann: Well, not necessarily. I mean, 1st class hackers can somehow create the breach themselves. But it&#8217;s pretty much all in the later part. Now you guys do remember that there have been instances like 15-year-old&#8217;s breaking into US intelligence chiefs and getting access to highly confidential information and further leaking it online. That&#8217;s what someone gifted with the knowledge of computers can do. I mean, I can try my whole life and not even get close to breaching a regular website, while a 15-year-old teenager can do that! You know what I mean?<br />Alex: I understand. He must be either someone very close to one of the bank&#8217;s managers to indirectly override the system somehow, with his help, without even letting him know. Or, he&#8217;s nothing but a pure hidden behind a computer screen.<br />Johann: I mean, yeah, yeah, um, that&#8217;s precisely how you can say that.<br />Alex: We should go to the bank.<br />McGill: Thank you, Mr. Johann. For your help. We&#8217;ll be contacting you again if necessary. Hope you don&#8217;t mind.<br />Johann: Oh, no. Not at all. I&#8217;ll be happy to help. I&#8217;ll do anything for my friend Alex here. After all, he saved me from jail once.<br />Miles: How? You&#8217;re in Berlin, and he&#8217;s from Russia.<br />Alex: That, Mr. Miles, I&#8217;ll tell you another day. Let&#8217;s go.<br />Johann: (Smiles) hmm.</p><p>The detectives and Officer McGill then reached the bank in their adjacent city.<br />McGill: (Showing badge to reception) Dublin PD, we need to talk with the manager.</p><p>They all then walked into the manager&#8217;s room. The manager was mid-aged, about 45. Whitebeard, dead-eye, looks under the glasses. The conversation oddly started as the manager looked and sounded pissed.</p><p>Manager: Where&#8217;s my money?<br />Alex: Oh, your money?<br />McGill: Detective Alex.<br />Manager: Yes, my money. I&#8217;ve hard-worked for this bank and put in many investments to build a reputation, and now they just come and told me that a 100 million dollar is gone! Just like that?<br />Miles: Obviously, you&#8217;re not in a good mindset right now. But you have to understand, there was a failure in your system.<br />Manager: What? My system? No, no, no, no, no….. I&#8217;ve seen bank managers who come to work and just sleep all day around sitting in their office. I don&#8217;t do that. I come here and pay attention to my staff and make sure they get work done. And yes, I am the one who&#8217;s robbed—10 years of glowing reputation.<br />Alex: Calm down. Introduce us to your staff because if you have a chance to get back your money, we have to work fast before the thief is gone with the money.<br />Manager: Okay. I just want it back. Anyhow. Please, detectives, do what you have to do. I&#8217;ll tell them to make a row.</p><p>Alex and Miles interrogated each of the staff to find nervous weaknesses and if they tried to lie or avoid any of their questions. Basically, simple questions like their work were in the bank and related to the money-transfer-server. They found two people held responsible for the money-transfer-server. But then again, the computer doesn&#8217;t recall them making any such transactions and yes, if they did, it can&#8217;t be deleted. It doesn&#8217;t work like that. So, you cannot accuse someone of doing something that has no legal proof. By their tone and accent, they seem pretty nervous but not as if guilty scared. Just nervous. So the detectives decided to leave it as it is for the day, as officer McGill was only informed about another case that happened somewhere. They equally agreed on surveilling the men related to the money transfer server, just in case something comes out. Else, they&#8217;ll just have to proceed to a higher investigation to find out if someone actually did, then who it could be, to leak the password in the first place.</p>						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-8d7f31a elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="8d7f31a" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-4f992a0" data-id="4f992a0" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-e648319 elementor-widget elementor-widget-heading" data-id="e648319" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="heading.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<h3 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">MAKE A DEDUCTION</h3>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-c1a4ac8 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="c1a4ac8" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-eb90285" data-id="eb90285" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-525cf4b elementor-widget elementor-widget-toggle" data-id="525cf4b" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="toggle.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-toggle" role="tablist">
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8631" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="1" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8631" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">HOW TO TRACE THE HACKER?</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8631" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="1" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8631"><p>They can just tell Johann to make a shortlist of the number of possible hackers he knows in the province who might do the job. And they did. And then they’ll later investigate them as well.</p></div>
				</div>
								</div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-79c0aeb elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="79c0aeb" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-aac9122" data-id="aac9122" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-2b4bbdf premium-lottie-canvas elementor-widget elementor-widget-premium-lottie" data-id="2b4bbdf" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="premium-lottie.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			
		<div class="premium-lottie-wrap">
			<div class="premium-lottie-animation" data-lottie-url="https://assets2.lottiefiles.com/packages/lf20_1joxr8cy.json" data-lottie-loop="true" data-lottie-reverse="" data-lottie-hover="" data-lottie-speed="1" data-lottie-render="canvas">
							</div>
		</div>

				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-bd539c7 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="bd539c7" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-9af7681" data-id="9af7681" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-1345de6 elementor-widget elementor-widget-html" data-id="1345de6" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="html.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<div id="disqus_thread"></div>
<script>
    (function() {
    var d = document, s = d.createElement('script');
    s.src = 'https://detectivemail.disqus.com/embed.js';
    s.setAttribute('data-timestamp', +new Date());
    (d.head || d.body).appendChild(s);
    })();
</script>
<noscript>Please enable JavaScript to view the <a href="https://disqus.com/?ref_noscript">comments powered by Disqus.</a></noscript>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
						</div>
					</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/mr-ghost-chapter-1/">Mr. Ghost | Chapter 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red</title>
		<link>https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/red/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Md Mazidul Haque Farabi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 19:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secret Killers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[author]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[case 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[red]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[secret killers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top rated]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/?p=1001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A week after, the only lead to OESZA was found dead. The detectives were just about to leave when the news of another mystery reached Dublin PD. This time the victim was a young businessman, and more shockingly, he had OESZA written in his body. Everyone believed that the criminal organization was back for more &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/red/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Red</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/red/">Red</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="1001" class="elementor elementor-1001" data-elementor-settings="[]">
							<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-3598bbe elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="3598bbe" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-d5c210d" data-id="d5c210d" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-691e3aa elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="691e3aa" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
															<img width="768" height="510" src="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/wp-content/uploads/red.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large" alt="" />															</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-08a4499 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="08a4499" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-57679ad" data-id="57679ad" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-bd9ccbe elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="bd9ccbe" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
								<p>A week after, the only lead to OESZA was found dead. The detectives were just about to leave when the news of another mystery reached Dublin PD. This time the victim was a young businessman, and more shockingly, he had OESZA written in his body. Everyone believed that the criminal organization was back for more action. But now the question was, why target a simple businessman after killing the MP? What could possibly be the real-time connection? And so it was somewhat good news and bad news for the two detectives. Their return flights were cancelled, and they were ordered to stay for further investigation into the case.</p><p>Detective Alex and Miles reached the place of the incident. It was a construction site of a really tall building. Though the guy who died had somehow tricked and pushed from one of the building&#8217;s top floors, shreds of evidence suggest that he was hit in the head with a heavy and pointed objected first. So they went up the stairs to the top floors, searching for evidence. And on one floor, they found his bag. So they were sure that this should be the floor from where he was hit in the head first and then pushed.</p><p>Detective Alex: Miles, What do you think?<br />Miles: Um, apart from the fact that the murderer decided to let us know where he killed him by leaving out his bag, I think he doubted that the man could survive a fall from such a tall height. Such a maniac.<br />Alex: Yes, why kill him first when he could&#8217;ve just made it look like a suicide? Unless they were engaged in a hand-to-hand fight and the murderer, saw no chance but to kill him first.<br />Miles: Could be, agreed. So they fought here. But why?<br />Alex: Perhaps because of something he had. Maybe in his bag.</p><p>They checked the bag of the victim and found a few clothes and nothing else.</p><p>Miles: You know, from the looks of the clothes, you can say it&#8217;s a –<br />Alex: Sleepover.<br />Miles: Exactly.<br />Alex: But what would you do in a construction site if you were planning for a sleepover?<br />Miles: Absolutely no idea.</p><p>The detectives found the mobile phone in the morgue with the dress he was wearing. Unfortunately, the phone was locked, and the IT section of Dublin PD couldn&#8217;t manage to crack the password and get into the phone by any means. It would require the same password, and it was the only way as they wanted to keep all the information intact and save the phone from factory reset for evidence. Finding no other information, they decided to search his address and so went to his home.</p><p>Alex: Observing the rooms, you know, you can tell a lot about a person.<br />Miles: Yeah. But all the unnecessary information that we already know. Single, 35, businessman, mid-income, a good taste in clothes and beer.<br />Alex: Yes, but; we missed something. That first OESZA case. The OESZA sign was written on the ground. But this time, it was written on his body.<br />Miles: Yeah. Maybe they decided to do it differently this time?<br />Alex: No, not that different. They could&#8217;ve also shot him like before, but they didn&#8217;t. I think we&#8217;re into something else.<br />Miles: Yeah, well, I&#8217;m bored. I wanted to go back to the US.<br />Alex: Homesick, are you.<br />Miles: Yeah. I mean, what is it with the Irish and beer. They drink so much.<br />Alex: Ah, I believe our guy is also a passionate drinker. Saying from his &#8216;antique&#8217; collection of bottles.<br />Miles: Don&#8217;t you think he&#8217;s a bit underpaid to live life like this?<br />Alex: No family, no other expenses; I am afraid I&#8217;d disagree. So, his phone has now automatically connected to the Wi-Fi.<br />Miles: You brought it with you?<br />Alex: Yes. Now, I think this guy could use the same password for everything. That means his phone too.<br />Miles: Why would you think that? I don&#8217;t.<br />Alex: Look at him. Does a business, didn&#8217;t study that much, doesn&#8217;t have a computer; I think he is a bit backdated.<br />Miles: Oh. I never thought about it from his dresses and collection of beer.<br />Alex: Oh, Miles, dresses and beer are just so 90s. You are an American; I thought you would understand better.<br />Miles: And yet apparently, I don&#8217;t. Continue.<br />Alex: If I could somehow crack his Wi-Fi password….um, what could it be? Miles: How would you know?<br />Alex: I don&#8217;t know how I would know! Let me think. If I&#8217;m lucky, I can get into his phone.<br />Miles: Okay, here we go again. You think you are Sherlock Holmes.<br />Alex: I don&#8217;t, and I told you that already.<br />Miles: Fine.<br />Alex: His favourite brand of Vodka, his famous suit tailor? What is it….</p><p>Alex started looking for clues in his home and guessed different passwords. While on the other hand, Miles went out and came back 5 minutes later, with the password.</p><p>Miles: It&#8217;s Jack6969.<br />Alex: What? How did you know that?<br />Miles: (Clears throat) Um, while you were busy trying to crack a password, you could never have even nearly got close enough in about one light-year; I used a simple technique.<br />Alex: What technique?<br />Miles: Well, I realized that his Wi-Fi speed was much more than his current speed. Which could only mean someone else was using his Wi-Fi. But you were not. I wasn&#8217;t. So who was?<br />Alex: Who?<br />Miles: Ah, it&#8217;s always the neighbourhood kid, Alex. I bribed him some candies, and he gave me the password. He told me he knows from a Halloween party when the guy had guests and got from one of the guests.<br />Alex: Quite brilliant, I suppose. Now, the moment of anticipation. Will it work? Yes!<br />Miles: Great. So?<br />Alex: Uber. It&#8217;s asking him to rate his last driver. And guess what, the last ride- 10.45pm.<br />Miles: What did the forensics tell about the time of his death?<br />Alex: 10.55pm.<br />Miles: Oh wow. Where was he picked off from?<br />Alex: From McLaren&#8217;s bar.<br />Miles: Let&#8217;s go.</p><p>They reached the bar and asked some people if they&#8217;d recognize the dead guy. One of them told them that he often came here and last he was with a girl. The girl also knew the girl, and so they reached the address.</p><p>Girl: Hi, how can I help you?<br />Alex: We&#8217;re here to talk about Jack. He&#8217;s dead.<br />Girl: Oh my God! I just met him last night.<br />Alex: You didn&#8217;t kill him, did you?<br />Girl: No, what? Why would I do that?<br />Alex: You took the last ride with him.<br />Girl: Yeah, but he dropped me off.<br />Alex: Oh really, then why did he have clothes for a sleepover?<br />Girl: I – don&#8217;t know!<br />Alex: You do know. You&#8217;re not that good a liar.<br />Girl: Oh yeah, my boyfriend died, and you&#8217;re accusing me? What proof do you have?<br />Alex: Boyfriend?<br />Girl: Well, I was sleeping with him.<br />Alex: Exactly. Then why did you guys skip last night?<br />Girl: Well, I wasn&#8217;t feeling well. I told him to drop me off.<br />Alex: We&#8217;ll see about that.<br />Miles: So, you&#8217;re a big fan of beer too, aren&#8217;t you?<br />The girl started weeping and crying and kept saying that she can&#8217;t believe that. Detective Alex didn&#8217;t buy a thing. Because he seriously doubted the girl.</p><p>Alex: So, you and Jack didn&#8217;t call each other last night?<br />Girl: No, ah, we contacted over messenger.<br />Alex: of Course!</p><p>Alex unlocked the phone again and went to his messenger app. He started reading texts.</p><p>Alex: So, you have a local accent. You spoke to John in completely another way.<br />Girl: Excuse me! Those are our private messages!<br />Alex: This is a part of a murder investigation, and it is serious evidence now, Ms. Lena.<br />Girl: (Crying)<br />Alex: So you liked most of his messages and didn&#8217;t reply. You were ignoring him. You have lots of typos; figures – long nails. And you eat dinner precisely at 10.00 pm every night.<br />Girl: How do you know that?<br />Alex: Specific typos. You thrice wrote &#8216;s&#8217; instead of &#8216;a&#8217; on 3 occasions at 10.00 and 10.01 pm. The one spelling mistake that people only make when typing with the left hand but is right-handed.<br />Girl: (Crying)<br />Miles: Stop crying. It won&#8217;t bring him back.<br />Girl: (Looks being shocked) you guys are so inhumane!<br />Alex: Why did you kill him?<br />Girl: l I told you already, I didn&#8217;t!<br />Alex: No, you did. Then you even wrote that on his body to confuse us. Last night you got in an Uber with Jack at 10.35. You eat dinner at 10.00. Your home is 6 kilometres from McLaren&#8217;s. You couldn&#8217;t possibly be there at 10.25 as you finish dinner at around 10.15.<br />Miles: 10.25?<br />Alex: No one leaves a bar before even passing 10 minutes. So, you ate dinner with him last night?<br />Girl: (No answer) keeps crying.<br />Alex: You took something from him. Something that was possibly in his bag. What was it? Something really valuable, I think. You murdered him for that. You guys got on the Uber. And then you took the Uber right where you planned. You guys are drinkers, so you somehow convinced him to get up the construction site with you and drink. I remember seeing a beer bottle of the same brand that I also saw in both of your houses, at the dustbin under the building. The brand is uncommon, and the scent at the bottle suggests a lady, and how I got the smell from a dustbin? Because the smell was yet fresh, and the dustbin was about empty. So, you killed him somehow at the top of the building, pushed him down, took the valuable thing from his bag by carefully opening it with your handkerchief because you didn&#8217;t want to leave out fingerprints.<br />Girl: Stop, you&#8217;re lying! I didn&#8217;t do any of that.<br />Alex: Oh, you did. Let me finish first. You took the thing, climbed downstairs, and took the back entry. You&#8217;re so confident and the challenging type, I guess. Because you didn&#8217;t flee from home. Of course, you know that would mean more spotlight of suspicion on you. And you didn&#8217;t want that.<br />Girl: Why would I kill him?<br />Alex: &#8220;Watch.&#8221; You told him to bring his watch last night, and he abnormally reacted, but you convinced him in the end. Unless, of course, you&#8217;re a smart girl, and you knew we could look his messages for evidence, and you accordingly gave that valuable thing a nickname so that you don&#8217;t get caught. And perhaps, Jack was also secret about that valuable thing. Maybe it was something he stole.<br />Girl: What are you saying? He was not a thief.<br />Alex: Anyway, where was I? So you took that last sip of the beer and dumped it in the dust bin on your way out through the back entrance after killing him. The dustbin is at the back entrance. The only reason there was no trash in the bin was that no one actually came there. The short road makes sense. And so that beer bottle from last night confirms it was you. And again, the scent and that small signs of lipstick, definitely not Jack. You walked away and came back right to your home like a cold-blooded murderer.<br />Girl: Stop! I didn&#8217;t do any of that. Why don&#8217;t you guys go and ask OESZA why they wrote that name on him!<br />Miles: Um, what did you say?<br />Alex: OESZA. Eureka.<br />Miles: Ms. Lena, you heard the news from us first, and you confirmed that. But we never mentioned OESZA.<br />Alex: Arrest her. She killed him.</p>						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-8d7f31a elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="8d7f31a" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-4f992a0" data-id="4f992a0" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-e648319 elementor-widget elementor-widget-heading" data-id="e648319" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="heading.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<h3 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">MAKE A DEDUCTION</h3>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-c1a4ac8 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="c1a4ac8" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-eb90285" data-id="eb90285" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-525cf4b elementor-widget elementor-widget-toggle" data-id="525cf4b" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="toggle.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-toggle" role="tablist">
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8631" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="1" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8631" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">DETECTIVE ALEX IS RIGHT</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8631" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="1" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8631"><p>Yes, Detective Alex was right all along. The girl killed him with her high heels first and stole a precious artifact from him. It was also stolen by Jack first, from a local museum.</p></div>
				</div>
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8632" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="2" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8632" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">DETECTIVE ALEX IS WRONG</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8632" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="2" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8632">No.</div>
				</div>
								</div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-79c0aeb elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="79c0aeb" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-aac9122" data-id="aac9122" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-2b4bbdf premium-lottie-canvas elementor-widget elementor-widget-premium-lottie" data-id="2b4bbdf" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="premium-lottie.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			
		<div class="premium-lottie-wrap">
			<div class="premium-lottie-animation" data-lottie-url="https://assets2.lottiefiles.com/packages/lf20_1joxr8cy.json" data-lottie-loop="true" data-lottie-reverse="" data-lottie-hover="" data-lottie-speed="1" data-lottie-render="canvas">
							</div>
		</div>

				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-bd539c7 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="bd539c7" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-9af7681" data-id="9af7681" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-1345de6 elementor-widget elementor-widget-html" data-id="1345de6" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="html.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<div id="disqus_thread"></div>
<script>
    (function() {
    var d = document, s = d.createElement('script');
    s.src = 'https://detectivemail.disqus.com/embed.js';
    s.setAttribute('data-timestamp', +new Date());
    (d.head || d.body).appendChild(s);
    })();
</script>
<noscript>Please enable JavaScript to view the <a href="https://disqus.com/?ref_noscript">comments powered by Disqus.</a></noscript>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
						</div>
					</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/red/">Red</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Detectives</title>
		<link>https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/two-detectives/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Md Mazidul Haque Farabi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 18:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Gangs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[author]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[case 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[criminal gangs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top rated]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[two detectives]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/?p=975</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The death of a local MP has shocked almost everyone, and now people are in full suspense about what might be going on. While you might think this was an act by the political beneficiaries of his death, everyone here, including officer McGill taking a sip of his morning coffee at the Dublin Police Department, &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/two-detectives/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Two Detectives</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/two-detectives/">Two Detectives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="975" class="elementor elementor-975" data-elementor-settings="[]">
							<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-3598bbe elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="3598bbe" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-d5c210d" data-id="d5c210d" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-691e3aa elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="691e3aa" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
															<img width="768" height="510" src="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/wp-content/uploads/two-detectives.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large" alt="" />															</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-08a4499 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="08a4499" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-57679ad" data-id="57679ad" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-bd9ccbe elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="bd9ccbe" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
								<p>The death of a local MP has shocked almost everyone, and now people are in full suspense about what might be going on. While you might think this was an act by the political beneficiaries of his death, everyone here, including officer McGill taking a sip of his morning coffee at the Dublin Police Department, is absolutely sure that it’s not. The case very certainly needed higher investigation, and so he had to make a call. He and his detective team had to reach a satisfactory reason, possibly with names, of the murder within 48-72 hours or risk being suspended. So he sought advice from his senior, and they both agreed upon bringing two qualified foreign detectives to help them investigate the case.</p><p>Detective Mr. Alexander Ivan from the Russian Crimes &amp; Forensics Branch and detective Kevin Miles from the New York Police Department arrived at Dublin on the first available flight to Dublin the next day. Though officer McGill wasn’t that worried about a Russian and an American working together, his senior did alert him about some of the problems he may have to face because of the distinct difference in nationalities. Although there was nothing, he could do as these two detectives were assigned by the higher security intelligence of the Irish Government upon his senior’s request. The detectives took different flights, but they were staying in two adjacent rooms of the same hotel.</p><p>At Dublin PD;</p><p>Officer McGill: Detective Miles, please take a seat.<br />Mr. Miles: Thank you, officer. So, I heard it’s pretty bad.<br />McGill: (Exhaling) It is. And the worst part is, we still have no clue on why, nothing at all.<br />Miles: Don’t worry, officer, we’ll find out something.<br />McGill: We better do.<br />Miles: Um, by the way, I heard the other guy’s Russian.<br />McGill: Yeah, I know, look, Mr. Alex is a great detective. And it’s just one case, don’t make any trouble, will you?<br />Miles: Oh, I’ll try my best, officer. But you know Russians.<br />McGill: So, we could’ve declared that it was suicide but, OESZA.<br />Miles: What is that?<br />McGill: Some kind of Criminal Organization, I don’t know. It was written with white paint on the street exactly where he died.<br />Miles: And you said there was no political involvement; why?<br />McGill: That is because MP Smith was a great guy. He had no competitors in Dublin in the last election. His family confirmed that he also had no such enmity with anyone that they could recall.<br />Miles: Understood.</p><p>Miles met the other detective, Mr. Ivan, in the hotel lobby. He would get his stuff from his room to investigate the crime scene, but he then thought they’ll both go together.</p><p>Miles: Hi, you must be detective Alex, from your Russian looks.<br />Alexander: First time we speak, and you had to bring that up.<br />Miles: Yeah. You must be 5 years older than me.<br />Alexander: And I request you behave that way.<br />Miles: Hum, okay.<br />Alexander: Now, do you have any updates on the case?<br />Miles: OESZA, that’s all we got.<br />Alexander: No relevant information on Google?<br />Miles: Nope.<br />Alexander: Let’s go.</p><p>They both reached the crime scene a few moments later. Alex started looking at the place of death highlighted by the cops. The area was nicely taped, and it was actually in the middle of a street-side market.</p><p>Alex: The criminal was an expert shooter. Could’ve shot anyone else, but he didn’t miss his target. This is definitely a criminal organization.<br />Miles: Could be a hitman.<br />Alex: You mean assassin?<br />Miles: Yes.<br />Alex: No. Assassins ought to take less risk. He could’ve shot him anywhere else, but he shot him here. In the middle of a market. Makes me think it was some sort of a distraction.<br />Miles: Create a distraction by killing the MP? Obviously, no way.<br />Alex: Unless, of course, OESZA wants to prove a point.<br />Miles: What kind of pint?<br />Alex: That they are capable of doing something like this.<br />Miles: Interesting. And what do you think they’ll gain by proving this point?<br />Alex: Fear.</p><p>They examined the place for any suspicious objects but found nothing.</p><p>Miles: The forensic results just came out.<br />Alex: M24?<br />Miles: Yes. How did you know?<br />Alex: The way his body fell tells us the angle he was shot. Look, top right corner. This means he was shot precisely from the opposite direction or the other supplementary angle.<br />Miles: Oh. And which is that way.<br />Alex: Exactly. And then look at the tall buildings that way. Two buildings. But the bullet wasn’t shot from the roof. Because first of all, it’s not that tall, and secondly, shooting him on the ground would mean lowering his gun quite a bit, which would mean someone definitely seeing him during the shot.<br />Miles: But the police confirmed that there were no eye suspects.<br />Alex: Yes, so, the shot was from that building, as the other building has permanently fixed glass windows and breaking any window would also mean an eye suspect though the shot was silenced.<br />Miles: Okay. So the shot was from that building, but how does that explain the type of the rifle?<br />Alex: I’m starting to think you are a novice, detective Miles. Images of the wound show the exact size of the bullet. And the distance of his body from the blood confirms that it was rather an M24, not an AWM.<br />Miles: All agreed. Except that I’m a novice.<br />Alex: Oh please, 15 cases, 10 successful. That might be satisfactory, but the inadequate amount of numbers shows your lack of experience.<br />Miles: Hum, so you researched me.<br />Alex: Of course I did; I’m not Sherlock Holmes.</p><p> </p><p>They both reached the morgue with officer McGill to watch Mr. Smith’s body more closely for any more details. Detective Miles has done a few courses on medical inspection, so he starts watching for bruises while Alex and officer McGill speak about the case.</p><p>McGill: Detective Alex, the OESZA writing on the road, the whole thing was planned by someone who knew exactly where he would be that day.<br />Alex: Yes. And for that, I’d need the CCTV footage.<br />McGill: I already saw that but found nothing to get on to. The angle of the CCTV doesn’t cover the exact place. There are about a thousand people buying things in that street.<br />Alex: Oh, no. I want the one on a block before, the connecting street with the main road. McGill: Okay. But, what will you do with that?<br />Alex: I have to see something. Miles, found anything?<br />Miles: No. The body is clean, no bruises, nothing.<br />Alex: Okay.</p><p>The CCTV footage arrived, and Alex saw it until they got Mr. Smith on the footage.</p><p>Alex: There. That’s all we need.<br />McGill: What?<br />Alex: That small speed breaker, it’s too hard to notice. I noticed that detective Miles here tripped on that. If he hadn’t, I also would’ve. It’s just too hard to notice.<br />Miles: Respectfully agreed.<br />McGill: Wait a minute, I also tripped there.<br />Alex: See the footage. About 2 in 5 people trip on that breaker. Point proved.<br />McGill: And those who don’t?<br />Miles: Their locales, or maybe they walk on this route every day.<br />Alex: Yes, exactly. Mr. Smith’s office isn’t that way; his home is also not this way. But, he used this road every day; for some reason. And the killer knew that. Which means he followed him for a few days to know his routine.<br />McGill: But my question is, why exactly here?<br />Miles: Oh, detective Alex already figured that out. OESZA is trying to make a name for itself.<br />McGill: Oh, God, I hope not.<br />Alex: Come on, let’s find the building where he was shot from.</p><p>They again arrive at the crime scene. Detective Alex stands at the point of the shot to find out the exact angle.</p><p>Miles: That’s impossible, mate.<br />Alex: Ah, I’m not your mate.<br />Miles: Oh yes, you are, detective Ivaraf.<br />Alex: You’re not supposed to know that name.<br />Miles: Well, now I do.<br />Alex: Okay, no big deal, you googled me. Congratulations! Now you know I’m a great detective.<br />Miles: Yes. But would you even tell that yourself after the Berlin triple murder case?<br />Alex: (Shocked) that’s not in google, is it?<br />Miles: No. But I’m not going to tell you how I got it.<br />Alex: I’ll find out myself.<br />Miles: Yeah, good luck with that.</p><p>They went to the third floor and stopped.</p><p>Alex: The shot must’ve been from 3D-<br />Miles: 3F, or 4D or 4F.<br />Alex: Yes.<br />Miles: Now?<br />Alex: Now we observe the people in these rooms. Because I believe anyone from these four flats is directly related to the murder.</p><p>They knock at each of the flats and found two families at 3D and 3F. Families can’t be related to this, so they move on to 4D and 4F. 4D was locked with no one living, so it was more or less suspicious, but they decided to check on that after confirming whether it was 4F or not. A person opened the door after they knocked.</p><p>4F guy: Yes, how may I help you?<br />Alex: We’re from your ISP, and we need to check your room’s wires as we think there might be a leak, and we need to find that.<br />4F guy: But I use cellular data.<br />Alex: Oh. In that case, there still might be a problem with the wires. Can we just check?</p><p>They checked the window, too, while acting like checking the wires. They got out without letting him know that they weren’t from the ISP.</p><p>Miles: (On the corridor) what do you think?<br />Alex: He might be our guy.<br />Miles: But I saw no traces of gunpowder.<br />Alex: Yes, but I know that. But else you didn’t saw?<br />Miles: What?<br />Alex: Dust. This week’s weather has been quite windy in Dublin, and the wind flows with speed through exactly this Northeast angle in this area, which is supposed to bring dust from outside.<br />Miles: Wow, um, maybe he cleaned it.<br />Alex: Oh, come on, he’s 25 max and lives alone. People don’t clean dust unless they have OCD, which he doesn’t, telling by how his room was.<br />Miles: So you’re confident.<br />Alex: Yeah, but just got to make sure of one more thing first. Since when he has been staying and where he works. Just to confirm.</p><p>They asked the building owner for more details on the 4F guy, and they got to know that he got in the apartment just a week ago and told them that he’d leave after a couple of months. They came out and started thinking.</p><p>Miles: Renting this flat for two months is too long for this case, Alex.<br />Alex: No, he has to at least avoid suspicion from the cops. He’s being paid in full for the stay by OESZA.<br />Miles: So he’s not the shooter?<br />Alex: No. His body isn’t the type who could shoot an M24 on a professional level. But he did look worried when we were checking the windows, you saw?<br />Miles: Yeah. We should arrest this guy.</p><p>They went up and knocked on 4F, but no one opened. After waiting for 3 minutes, Miles broke the lock. As supposed, no one was inside. They quickly looked down the window and could find the 4F guy sliding through the pipe and started running away. So they both went after him climbing down the stairs. The chase was on. But he was getting far away. So detective Miles stopped and aimed his gun at him and shot. But he missed, and the guy ran away into more people in a busy street. They searched, but couldn’t find him, so they went back to Dublin PD.</p><p>McGill: Andy O’Brian. Not from this city. But we will find him.<br />Miles: He heard us and ran away.<br />McGill: Don’t worry, we’ll get him.<br />Alex: But you won’t get any information off him.<br />McGill: Why?<br />Alex: Because you’ll find him dead. If they could kill the MP in public, they’d kill him anywhere, just not to risk the leakage of any more information about their gang.<br />McGill: Oh. But I disagree with you, Mr. Alex. And supposing even if they intend to do that, I believe we’ll find him before they can.<br />Alex: Let’s just wait and watch.</p>						</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-8d7f31a elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="8d7f31a" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-4f992a0" data-id="4f992a0" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-e648319 elementor-widget elementor-widget-heading" data-id="e648319" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="heading.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<h3 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">MAKE A DEDUCTION</h3>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-c1a4ac8 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="c1a4ac8" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-eb90285" data-id="eb90285" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-525cf4b elementor-widget elementor-widget-toggle" data-id="525cf4b" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="toggle.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-toggle" role="tablist">
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8631" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="1" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8631" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">OFFICER McGILL IS RIGHT</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8631" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="1" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8631"><p>Wrong.</p></div>
				</div>
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8632" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="2" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8632" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">DETECTIVE ALEX IS RIGHT</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8632" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="2" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8632"><p>Detective Alex was right.<br /><br />The boy was found dead the same day. Though they couldn’t get anything on OESZA, officer McGill saved his job after declaring the boy as “one of the” killers in the press briefing. Alex and Miles stayed in Dublin and further investigated the boy’s body, but this time he was stabbed. OESZA remains a complete mystery.</p></div>
				</div>
								</div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-79c0aeb elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="79c0aeb" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-aac9122" data-id="aac9122" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-2b4bbdf premium-lottie-canvas elementor-widget elementor-widget-premium-lottie" data-id="2b4bbdf" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="premium-lottie.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			
		<div class="premium-lottie-wrap">
			<div class="premium-lottie-animation" data-lottie-url="https://assets2.lottiefiles.com/packages/lf20_1joxr8cy.json" data-lottie-loop="true" data-lottie-reverse="" data-lottie-hover="" data-lottie-speed="1" data-lottie-render="canvas">
							</div>
		</div>

				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-bd539c7 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="bd539c7" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-9af7681" data-id="9af7681" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-1345de6 elementor-widget elementor-widget-html" data-id="1345de6" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="html.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<div id="disqus_thread"></div>
<script>
    (function() {
    var d = document, s = d.createElement('script');
    s.src = 'https://detectivemail.disqus.com/embed.js';
    s.setAttribute('data-timestamp', +new Date());
    (d.head || d.body).appendChild(s);
    })();
</script>
<noscript>Please enable JavaScript to view the <a href="https://disqus.com/?ref_noscript">comments powered by Disqus.</a></noscript>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
						</div>
					</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail/two-detectives/">Two Detectives</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://mazidulfarabi.github.io/detectivemail">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
