<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>case 2 &#8211; Detectivemail</title>
	<atom:link href="https://detectivemail.com/tag/case-2/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://detectivemail.com</link>
	<description>Crime Stories</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 20:11:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://detectivemail.com/wp-content/uploads/detectivemail-logo.jpg</url>
	<title>case 2 &#8211; Detectivemail</title>
	<link>https://detectivemail.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Red</title>
		<link>https://detectivemail.com/red/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Md Mazidul Haque Farabi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 19:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Cases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secret Killers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[author]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[case 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[red]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[secret killers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[top rated]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://detectivemail.com/?p=1001</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A week after, the only lead to OESZA was found dead. The detectives were just about to leave when the news of another mystery reached Dublin PD. This time the victim was a young businessman, and more shockingly, he had OESZA written in his body. Everyone believed that the criminal organization was back for more &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://detectivemail.com/red/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Red</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://detectivemail.com/red/">Red</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://detectivemail.com">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="wp-post" data-elementor-id="1001" class="elementor elementor-1001" data-elementor-settings="[]">
							<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-3598bbe elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="3598bbe" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-d5c210d" data-id="d5c210d" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-691e3aa elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-id="691e3aa" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="768" height="510" src="https://detectivemail.com/wp-content/uploads/red.jpg" class="attachment-medium_large size-medium_large" alt="" loading="lazy" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-08a4499 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="08a4499" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-57679ad" data-id="57679ad" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-bd9ccbe elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-id="bd9ccbe" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><p>A week after, the only lead to OESZA was found dead. The detectives were just about to leave when the news of another mystery reached Dublin PD. This time the victim was a young businessman, and more shockingly, he had OESZA written in his body. Everyone believed that the criminal organization was back for more action. But now the question was, why target a simple businessman after killing the MP? What could possibly be the real-time connection? And so it was somewhat good news and bad news for the two detectives. Their return flights were cancelled, and they were ordered to stay for further investigation into the case.</p><p>Detective Alex and Miles reached the place of the incident. It was a construction site of a really tall building. Though the guy who died had somehow tricked and pushed from one of the building&#8217;s top floors, shreds of evidence suggest that he was hit in the head with a heavy and pointed objected first. So they went up the stairs to the top floors, searching for evidence. And on one floor, they found his bag. So they were sure that this should be the floor from where he was hit in the head first and then pushed.</p><p>Detective Alex: Miles, What do you think?<br />Miles: Um, apart from the fact that the murderer decided to let us know where he killed him by leaving out his bag, I think he doubted that the man could survive a fall from such a tall height. Such a maniac.<br />Alex: Yes, why kill him first when he could&#8217;ve just made it look like a suicide? Unless they were engaged in a hand-to-hand fight and the murderer, saw no chance but to kill him first.<br />Miles: Could be, agreed. So they fought here. But why?<br />Alex: Perhaps because of something he had. Maybe in his bag.</p><p>They checked the bag of the victim and found a few clothes and nothing else.</p><p>Miles: You know, from the looks of the clothes, you can say it&#8217;s a –<br />Alex: Sleepover.<br />Miles: Exactly.<br />Alex: But what would you do in a construction site if you were planning for a sleepover?<br />Miles: Absolutely no idea.</p><p>The detectives found the mobile phone in the morgue with the dress he was wearing. Unfortunately, the phone was locked, and the IT section of Dublin PD couldn&#8217;t manage to crack the password and get into the phone by any means. It would require the same password, and it was the only way as they wanted to keep all the information intact and save the phone from factory reset for evidence. Finding no other information, they decided to search his address and so went to his home.</p><p>Alex: Observing the rooms, you know, you can tell a lot about a person.<br />Miles: Yeah. But all the unnecessary information that we already know. Single, 35, businessman, mid-income, a good taste in clothes and beer.<br />Alex: Yes, but; we missed something. That first OESZA case. The OESZA sign was written on the ground. But this time, it was written on his body.<br />Miles: Yeah. Maybe they decided to do it differently this time?<br />Alex: No, not that different. They could&#8217;ve also shot him like before, but they didn&#8217;t. I think we&#8217;re into something else.<br />Miles: Yeah, well, I&#8217;m bored. I wanted to go back to the US.<br />Alex: Homesick, are you.<br />Miles: Yeah. I mean, what is it with the Irish and beer. They drink so much.<br />Alex: Ah, I believe our guy is also a passionate drinker. Saying from his &#8216;antique&#8217; collection of bottles.<br />Miles: Don&#8217;t you think he&#8217;s a bit underpaid to live life like this?<br />Alex: No family, no other expenses; I am afraid I&#8217;d disagree. So, his phone has now automatically connected to the Wi-Fi.<br />Miles: You brought it with you?<br />Alex: Yes. Now, I think this guy could use the same password for everything. That means his phone too.<br />Miles: Why would you think that? I don&#8217;t.<br />Alex: Look at him. Does a business, didn&#8217;t study that much, doesn&#8217;t have a computer; I think he is a bit backdated.<br />Miles: Oh. I never thought about it from his dresses and collection of beer.<br />Alex: Oh, Miles, dresses and beer are just so 90s. You are an American; I thought you would understand better.<br />Miles: And yet apparently, I don&#8217;t. Continue.<br />Alex: If I could somehow crack his Wi-Fi password….um, what could it be? Miles: How would you know?<br />Alex: I don&#8217;t know how I would know! Let me think. If I&#8217;m lucky, I can get into his phone.<br />Miles: Okay, here we go again. You think you are Sherlock Holmes.<br />Alex: I don&#8217;t, and I told you that already.<br />Miles: Fine.<br />Alex: His favourite brand of Vodka, his famous suit tailor? What is it….</p><p>Alex started looking for clues in his home and guessed different passwords. While on the other hand, Miles went out and came back 5 minutes later, with the password.</p><p>Miles: It&#8217;s Jack6969.<br />Alex: What? How did you know that?<br />Miles: (Clears throat) Um, while you were busy trying to crack a password, you could never have even nearly got close enough in about one light-year; I used a simple technique.<br />Alex: What technique?<br />Miles: Well, I realized that his Wi-Fi speed was much more than his current speed. Which could only mean someone else was using his Wi-Fi. But you were not. I wasn&#8217;t. So who was?<br />Alex: Who?<br />Miles: Ah, it&#8217;s always the neighbourhood kid, Alex. I bribed him some candies, and he gave me the password. He told me he knows from a Halloween party when the guy had guests and got from one of the guests.<br />Alex: Quite brilliant, I suppose. Now, the moment of anticipation. Will it work? Yes!<br />Miles: Great. So?<br />Alex: Uber. It&#8217;s asking him to rate his last driver. And guess what, the last ride- 10.45pm.<br />Miles: What did the forensics tell about the time of his death?<br />Alex: 10.55pm.<br />Miles: Oh wow. Where was he picked off from?<br />Alex: From McLaren&#8217;s bar.<br />Miles: Let&#8217;s go.</p><p>They reached the bar and asked some people if they&#8217;d recognize the dead guy. One of them told them that he often came here and last he was with a girl. The girl also knew the girl, and so they reached the address.</p><p>Girl: Hi, how can I help you?<br />Alex: We&#8217;re here to talk about Jack. He&#8217;s dead.<br />Girl: Oh my God! I just met him last night.<br />Alex: You didn&#8217;t kill him, did you?<br />Girl: No, what? Why would I do that?<br />Alex: You took the last ride with him.<br />Girl: Yeah, but he dropped me off.<br />Alex: Oh really, then why did he have clothes for a sleepover?<br />Girl: I – don&#8217;t know!<br />Alex: You do know. You&#8217;re not that good a liar.<br />Girl: Oh yeah, my boyfriend died, and you&#8217;re accusing me? What proof do you have?<br />Alex: Boyfriend?<br />Girl: Well, I was sleeping with him.<br />Alex: Exactly. Then why did you guys skip last night?<br />Girl: Well, I wasn&#8217;t feeling well. I told him to drop me off.<br />Alex: We&#8217;ll see about that.<br />Miles: So, you&#8217;re a big fan of beer too, aren&#8217;t you?<br />The girl started weeping and crying and kept saying that she can&#8217;t believe that. Detective Alex didn&#8217;t buy a thing. Because he seriously doubted the girl.</p><p>Alex: So, you and Jack didn&#8217;t call each other last night?<br />Girl: No, ah, we contacted over messenger.<br />Alex: of Course!</p><p>Alex unlocked the phone again and went to his messenger app. He started reading texts.</p><p>Alex: So, you have a local accent. You spoke to John in completely another way.<br />Girl: Excuse me! Those are our private messages!<br />Alex: This is a part of a murder investigation, and it is serious evidence now, Ms. Lena.<br />Girl: (Crying)<br />Alex: So you liked most of his messages and didn&#8217;t reply. You were ignoring him. You have lots of typos; figures – long nails. And you eat dinner precisely at 10.00 pm every night.<br />Girl: How do you know that?<br />Alex: Specific typos. You thrice wrote &#8216;s&#8217; instead of &#8216;a&#8217; on 3 occasions at 10.00 and 10.01 pm. The one spelling mistake that people only make when typing with the left hand but is right-handed.<br />Girl: (Crying)<br />Miles: Stop crying. It won&#8217;t bring him back.<br />Girl: (Looks being shocked) you guys are so inhumane!<br />Alex: Why did you kill him?<br />Girl: l I told you already, I didn&#8217;t!<br />Alex: No, you did. Then you even wrote that on his body to confuse us. Last night you got in an Uber with Jack at 10.35. You eat dinner at 10.00. Your home is 6 kilometres from McLaren&#8217;s. You couldn&#8217;t possibly be there at 10.25 as you finish dinner at around 10.15.<br />Miles: 10.25?<br />Alex: No one leaves a bar before even passing 10 minutes. So, you ate dinner with him last night?<br />Girl: (No answer) keeps crying.<br />Alex: You took something from him. Something that was possibly in his bag. What was it? Something really valuable, I think. You murdered him for that. You guys got on the Uber. And then you took the Uber right where you planned. You guys are drinkers, so you somehow convinced him to get up the construction site with you and drink. I remember seeing a beer bottle of the same brand that I also saw in both of your houses, at the dustbin under the building. The brand is uncommon, and the scent at the bottle suggests a lady, and how I got the smell from a dustbin? Because the smell was yet fresh, and the dustbin was about empty. So, you killed him somehow at the top of the building, pushed him down, took the valuable thing from his bag by carefully opening it with your handkerchief because you didn&#8217;t want to leave out fingerprints.<br />Girl: Stop, you&#8217;re lying! I didn&#8217;t do any of that.<br />Alex: Oh, you did. Let me finish first. You took the thing, climbed downstairs, and took the back entry. You&#8217;re so confident and the challenging type, I guess. Because you didn&#8217;t flee from home. Of course, you know that would mean more spotlight of suspicion on you. And you didn&#8217;t want that.<br />Girl: Why would I kill him?<br />Alex: &#8220;Watch.&#8221; You told him to bring his watch last night, and he abnormally reacted, but you convinced him in the end. Unless, of course, you&#8217;re a smart girl, and you knew we could look his messages for evidence, and you accordingly gave that valuable thing a nickname so that you don&#8217;t get caught. And perhaps, Jack was also secret about that valuable thing. Maybe it was something he stole.<br />Girl: What are you saying? He was not a thief.<br />Alex: Anyway, where was I? So you took that last sip of the beer and dumped it in the dust bin on your way out through the back entrance after killing him. The dustbin is at the back entrance. The only reason there was no trash in the bin was that no one actually came there. The short road makes sense. And so that beer bottle from last night confirms it was you. And again, the scent and that small signs of lipstick, definitely not Jack. You walked away and came back right to your home like a cold-blooded murderer.<br />Girl: Stop! I didn&#8217;t do any of that. Why don&#8217;t you guys go and ask OESZA why they wrote that name on him!<br />Miles: Um, what did you say?<br />Alex: OESZA. Eureka.<br />Miles: Ms. Lena, you heard the news from us first, and you confirmed that. But we never mentioned OESZA.<br />Alex: Arrest her. She killed him.</p></div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-8d7f31a elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="8d7f31a" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-4f992a0" data-id="4f992a0" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-e648319 elementor-widget elementor-widget-heading" data-id="e648319" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="heading.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<h3 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">MAKE A DEDUCTION</h3>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-c1a4ac8 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="c1a4ac8" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-eb90285" data-id="eb90285" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-525cf4b elementor-widget elementor-widget-toggle" data-id="525cf4b" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="toggle.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-toggle" role="tablist">
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8631" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="1" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8631" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">DETECTIVE ALEX IS RIGHT</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8631" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="1" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8631"><p>Yes, Detective Alex was right all along. The girl killed him with her high heels first and stole a precious artifact from him. It was also stolen by Jack first, from a local museum.</p></div>
				</div>
							<div class="elementor-toggle-item">
					<div id="elementor-tab-title-8632" class="elementor-tab-title" data-tab="2" role="tab" aria-controls="elementor-tab-content-8632" aria-expanded="false">
												<span class="elementor-toggle-icon elementor-toggle-icon-left" aria-hidden="true">
															<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-closed"><i class="fas fa-caret-right"></i></span>
								<span class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened"><i class="elementor-toggle-icon-opened fas fa-caret-up"></i></span>
													</span>
												<a href="" class="elementor-toggle-title">DETECTIVE ALEX IS WRONG</a>
					</div>
					<div id="elementor-tab-content-8632" class="elementor-tab-content elementor-clearfix" data-tab="2" role="tabpanel" aria-labelledby="elementor-tab-title-8632">No.</div>
				</div>
					</div>
				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-79c0aeb elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="79c0aeb" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-aac9122" data-id="aac9122" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-2b4bbdf premium-lottie-canvas elementor-widget elementor-widget-premium-lottie" data-id="2b4bbdf" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="premium-lottie.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			
		<div class="premium-lottie-wrap">
			<div class="premium-lottie-animation" data-lottie-url="https://assets2.lottiefiles.com/packages/lf20_1joxr8cy.json" data-lottie-loop="true" data-lottie-reverse="" data-lottie-hover="" data-lottie-speed="1" data-lottie-render="canvas">
							</div>
		</div>

				</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
				<section class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-bd539c7 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default" data-id="bd539c7" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
					<div class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-9af7681" data-id="9af7681" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
								<div class="elementor-element elementor-element-1345de6 elementor-widget elementor-widget-html" data-id="1345de6" data-element_type="widget" data-widget_type="html.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<div id="disqus_thread"></div>
<script>
    (function() {
    var d = document, s = d.createElement('script');
    s.src = 'https://detectivemail.disqus.com/embed.js';
    s.setAttribute('data-timestamp', +new Date());
    (d.head || d.body).appendChild(s);
    })();
</script>
<noscript>Please enable JavaScript to view the <a href="https://disqus.com/?ref_noscript">comments powered by Disqus.</a></noscript>		</div>
				</div>
					</div>
		</div>
							</div>
		</section>
						</div>
					</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://detectivemail.com/red/">Red</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://detectivemail.com">Detectivemail</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
